Now let's look at the grep command.
So there are many commands available or different types of files.
So for example, c grep will search all the c C++ files, g grep will search all the gradle files,
go grep will search all the go files.
Similarly j grep for java katie grep for kotlin resource grep to search the example files and to search
the manifest man grep rm grep to search the make files and the beep files on grep to search all the
owner's files.
So there are some files which is named owners in Aosp.
So it will contain the name of the owner of the module.
So it will be mostly an email address, some employee within Google.
So you can search those files with own grep and ask grep is to search the rust files sep crap is to
search the sap s policy files.
That is the standard extension files.
Then s grep is to search all the local source files.
So we have these many variants of grep.
So let's try a few of them.
Let's first search the C++ files, the C grep, C or C++ files.
Maybe my file should be something with y.
Yeah.
This will show all the CP files where we have the wi fi keyword.
So there are a lot of files and slate.
Now try the g grep.
Not really sure how many gradle files are there, but let's search for dependencies.
Okay.
So this will search all the gradle files with the word dependencies.
That's good.
Okay.
Now go grep is to search the go files in.
Not sure what I search for here.
Search for wi fi.
It sells for wi fi.
Yeah.
So there are some go files with my file.
And similarly j scripts search sys ui to show all the modules or the system ui modules basically and
select.
And similarly, kate grep shows circuit files showing all the case files.
Then we have rest grep the source files.
So inside this list, search for constrain layout, there should be some resources with constraint layout.
The layout files, here you go.
And now we have main grep.
GREP is for searching the manifest files.
So inside manifest file search for application tag right here you go there.
And then we have m grep just to search make files or beep files so they are search for java.
So it will search for the beep and make files.
And then we have own grep here.
You can search for the or with the owner's name like let's search for Dom.
You hope there will be someone with the name dom Tom Taylor at google dot com.
These are from automotive.
Yeah it shows you google.com so it will search only the owner files search rest files are as grep search
five five anything.
Yeah.
So there are some with my files.
So this will search all the files with extension address which are the rust files and to search the
zip policy sep rep.
So within a C policy we could search for maybe read this should ideally show all the starter files.
Yeah car service, CVS app.
And finally we have s grep and let's search my file here.
And so this will show all the files, XML, C++, Rust, Java, SC, everything.
Okay.
So these are sometimes handy when you are using terminal window.